freefoto.com 2000-12-06

# Privacy Policy - Free Pictures - FreeFoto.Com.

 Privacy Policy

FreeFoto.com, and its advertisers and affiliates are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below is information outlining our continued support for the responsible management of consumer information.

Consumer Information

During the process of delivering a page to you, FreeFoto.com does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, FreeFoto.com does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information collected by FreeFoto.com is used for the purpose of further developing and building the site.

In some cases, you may voluntarily provide personal information in response to a specific page. This information is used by FreeFoto.com to respond to your request. In addition, FreeFoto.com may combine this information with other users' information and review it in an aggregate form to understand the type of individuals who view a specific type of ad or visit a particular kind of website.

Data Collection and Opt Out

FreeFoto.com, as well as most sites on the Internet, use "cookies" to enhance your experience on the web. FreeFoto.com cannot use these cookies to personally identify you in any way. What are cookies and why do we use them? A cookie is a unique number that is provided to you the first time FreeFoto.com serves you a page. This unique number, which is stored in a cookie file on your computer, helps FreeFoto.com and help our advertisers understand what you like and don't like about their offerings so that they can cater better to your needs the next time you are interested in their products or services. While we believe that cookies enhance your Internet experience by limiting the number of times you see the same ad and delivering more relevant content to you, they are not required for FreeFoto.com to deliver you a page.

If you do not want the benefit of cookies, there is a simple procedure to manually delete your cookies. Please consult your web browser's Help documentation for more information.

Opt Out Procedure

If you would like to "opt out," that is, to prevent any data from being stored by FreeFoto.com , please click here.

Participation in Industry-side Privacy Initiatives

If you have any additional questions about FreeFoto.com's dedication to consumer privacy, please contact us at info@freefoto.com.

FreeFoto works with a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Flycast manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.flycast.com/about_us/about-privacy.html>
